<movies>
	<movie>
		<title>Demolition Man</title>
		<length>115</length>
		<year>1993</year>
		<synopsis>
			Although the initial scenes are set in a dystopian version
			of Los Angeles, circa 1996 (which was 3 years in the future,
			at the time of the movie's release), most of the film is set
			in the year 2032, where San Angeles, California has become a
			peaceful, sanitized paradise. In the film, San Angeles has
			been created from the joining of Los Angeles, Santa Barbara,
			San Diego and the surrounding metropolitan regions following
			a massive earthquake in 2010. Simon Phoenix (Wesley Snipes)
			is incarcerated in a "cryoprison" that keeps its prisoners
			cryonically frozen in suspended animation as a sentence for
			his activities as a crime lord in 1990s Los Angeles. He
			escapes during a parole hearing and soon embarks on a reign
			of terror throughout the city of San Angeles. Because police
			officers no longer know how to deal with violent criminals,
			supercop Sgt. John Spartan (Sylvester Stallone), aka "The
			Demolition Man", is paroled from the cryoprison for the
			purpose of apprehending Phoenix. Spartan owes his 36-year
			term in the cryoprison to Phoenix—while trying to capture
			Phoenix in 1996, Spartan destroyed his headquarters and
			allegedly killed a busload of passengers Phoenix was holding
			as hostages. Phoenix lied to the police and said that he had
			warned Spartan about the hostages, while in reality (as
			Phoenix later revealed) they were already dead and cold,
			thus rendering them invisible to Spartan's thermoscan. The
			authorities chose to believe Phoenix's rendition of events
			given their knowledge of Spartan's devil-may-care attitude
			and Spartan was made the scapegoat.
		</synopsis>
	
		<director>Marco Brambilla</director>
		
		<actor>Sylvester Stallone</actor>
		<actor>Wesley Snipes</actor>
		<actor>Sandra Bullock</actor>
		<actor>Nigel Hawthorne</actor>
		<actor>Denis Leary</actor>
		
		<genre>science fiction</genre>
		<genre>action</genre>
		<genre>comedy</genre>
	</movie>
    
    <movie>
		<title>Cop Land</title>
		<length>104</length>
		<year>1997</year>
		<synopsis>
			The film takes place in fictional Garrison, New Jersey, a
			small town across the Hudson River from New York near the
			George Washington Bridge where a large number of residents
			are New York City Police Department officers. Stallone plays
			the quiet Freddy Heflin, the hearing impaired sheriff of
			Garrison who admires his friends who are cops. Helfin had
			wanted to join the NYPD but was rejected due to his injury.
			Although nominally the sheriff, Freddy's actual authority is
			limited to handling minor civil issues, the real power in
			town being wielded by corrupt NYPD cops, primarily Ray
			Donlan (Keitel) who constantly reminds Freddy that he is
			only a local sheriff and is not really one of them.
			Consequently Heflin spends most of his days listening to his
			vinyl records and longing for his high school sweetheart
			(Annabella Sciorra) whom Freddy saved from drowning at the
			cost of his hearing and who dumped him for a dysfunctional
			marriage with another cop, Joey Randone (Peter Berg).
			Matters are further complicated by 'Figgsy' (Liotta) another
			corrupt NYPD officer but a friend of Freddy's and someone at
			a crossroads trying to change and do the right thing. Figgsy
			also has an ongoing rift with Randone.

			De Niro plays Lt Moe Tilden, an NYPD internal affairs
			officer investigating Mafia connected corruption amongst the
			officers living in Garrison. His jurisdiction ends at the
			George Washington Bridge but the men he watches live across
			that bridge. His investigation gets a break when one of the
			cops, Murray 'Superboy' Babitch (Michael Rapaport) causes
			the deaths of two unarmed motorists and when another corrupt
			cop is caught red handed trying to plant a weapon on one of
			deceased motorists to justify the shooting. Their fellow
			corrupt cops (Harvey Keitel, Robert Patrick, John Spencer
			and Arthur J. Nascarella) fear Babitch will testify to
			internal affairs about police corruption and so fake his
			death and put him in hiding.
		</synopsis>

		<director>James Mangold</director>

		
		<actor>Sylvester Stallone</actor>
		<actor>Ray Liotta</actor>
		<actor>Harvey Keitel</actor>
		<actor>Peter Berg</actor>
		<actor>Robert Patrick</actor>
		
		<genre>drama</genre>

	</movie>
	
	<movie>
		<title>Walk the Line</title>
		<length>135</length>
		<year>2005</year>
		<synopsis>
			The film details Johnny Cash's life from his growing up as
			the son of a cotton picker in Dyess, Arkansas, dealing with
			the death of his brother, his drug addiction, subsequent
			rescue by future wife June Carter, and his famous concert at
			Folsom State Prison.

			The film opens in medias res with an exterior shot of Folsom
			Prison. The grounds are quiet except for the faint sound of
			music. Two guards on their tower peer at the main building.
			As we slowly approach the main building, the music begins to
			increase in volume. The camera tracks past empty cells and
			halls as the music becomes louder and more distinct; now
			cheering can be heard. Finally we see the source of the
			cheering: an audience of inmates for Johnny Cash's band,
			which is playing a vamp. In the next shot, a table saw rests
			on a table as a hand casually strokes the blade. After
			repeated calls, we are made aware that the hand is that of
			Johnny Cash. (Later we learn that the voice calling him
			onstage is that of the prison warden.)

			In the next scene, Cash is a boy. (His legal name was "J. R.
			Cash", as he did not adopt the name "John" until entering
			the Air Force.) He and his brother Jack are listening to the
			radio; the 10-year-old June Carter is singing.
		</synopsis>

		<director>James Mangold</director>
		
		<actor>Joaquin Phoenix</actor>
		<actor>Reese Witherspoon</actor>
		<actor>Ginnifer Goodwin</actor>
		<actor>Robert Patrick</actor>
	
		<genre>biography</genre>
		<genre>drama</genre>
		
	</movie>
        
        
        
        

</movies>